The war in Gaza has killed more than 11,000 Palestinians in just over a month and created a humanitarian disaster.
Israeli officials have said this work for months or even years.
Have you communicated to Prime Minister Netanyahu any sort of deadline or time frame for how long you are willing to support Israel in this operation?
Are you comfortable with the operation going on indefinitely, and is there any deal underway to free us?
Thank you.
Yes, no, working backwards, forward.
Look, I have been deeply involved in moving on the hostage negotiation, and I don't want to get ahead of myself here because I don't know what's happened in the last four hours.
But I have gotten great cooperation from the Qataris.
I've spoken with them as well a number of times.
I think the pause that the Israelis have agreed to, it's down to, I'm getting too much detail.
I know, Mr. Secretary, I'm going to stop.
But I am mildly hopeful.
I'm mildly hopeful.